<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Compose App</string>
    <string name="woof_app_name">Woof</string>
    <string name="title_activity_compose_article">ComposeArticleActivity</string>
    <string name="article_title">Jetpack Compose Tutorial</string>
    <string name="article_first_text">Jetpack Compose is a modern toolkit for building native Android UI. Compose simplifies and accelerates UI development on Android with less code, powerful tools, and intuitive Kotlin APIs.</string>
    <string name="article_second_text">In this tutorial, you build a simple UI component with declarative functions. You call Compose functions to say what elements you want and the Compose compiler does the rest. Compose is built around Composable functions. These functions let you define your app\\\'s UI programmatically because they let you describe how it should look and provide data dependencies, rather than focus on the process of the UI\\\'s construction, such as initializing an element and then attaching it to a parent. To create a Composable function, you add the @Composable annotation to the function name.</string>
    <string name="first_title">Text composable</string>
    <string name="first_description">Displays text and follows the recommended Material Design guidelines.</string>
    <string name="second_title">Image composable</string>
    <string name="second_description">Creates a composable that lays out and draws a given Painter class object.</string>
    <string name="third_title">Row composable</string>
    <string name="third_description">A layout composable that places its children in a horizontal sequence.</string>
    <string name="fourth_title">Column composable</string>
    <string name="fourth_description">A layout composable that places its children in a vertical sequence.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dice_roller">DiceRollerActivity</string>

    <string name="roll">Roll</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lemonade">LemonadeActivity</string>
    <string name="lemon_select">Tap the lemon tree to select a lemon</string>
    <string name="lemon_tree_content_description">Lemon tree</string>
    <string name="lemon_squeeze">Keep tapping the lemon to squeeze it</string>
    <string name="lemon_squeeze_content_description">Lemon Squeeze</string>
    <string name="lemon_drink">Tap the lemonade to drink it</string>
    <string name="lemon_drink_content_description">Glass of lemonade</string>
    <string name="lemon_empty">Tap the empty glass to start again</string>
    <string name="lemon_restart_content_description">Empty glass</string>

    <string name="tip_time">Tip Time</string>
    <string name="calculate_tip">Calculate Tip</string>
    <string name="bill_amount">Bill Amount</string>
    <string name="tip_amount">Tip Amount: %s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tip_time">TipTimeActivity</string>
    <string name="how_was_the_service">Tip Percentage</string>
    <string name="round_up_tip">Round up tip?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_art_space">ArtSpaceActivity</string>
    <string name="girl_with_pearl_desc">Girl with a Pearl Earring (Dutch: Meisje met de parel) is an oil painting by Dutch Golden Age painter Johannes Vermeer, dated c. 1665. Going by various names over the centuries, it became known by its present title towards the end of the 20th century because of the earring worn by the girl portrayed there.[3] The work has been in the collection of the Mauritshuis in The Hague since 1902 and has been the subject of various literary and cinematic treatments.</string>
    <string name="the_persistence_of_memory_desc">The Persistence of Memory (Catalan: La persistència de la memòria, Spanish: La persistencia de la memoria) is a 1931 painting by artist Salvador Dalí and one of the most recognizable works of Surrealism. First shown at the Julien Levy Gallery in 1932, since 1934 the painting has been in the collection of the Museum of Modern Art (MoMA) in New York City, which received it from an anonymous donor. It is widely recognized and frequently referred to in popular culture,[1] and sometimes referred to by more descriptive titles, such as \"The Melting Clocks\", \"The Soft Watches\" or \"The Melting Watches\".</string>
    <string name="the_scream_desc">The Scream is an art composition created by Norwegian artist Edvard Munch in 1893. The Norwegian name of the piece is Skrik (\'Scream\'), and the German title under which it was first exhibited is Der Schrei der Natur (\'The Scream of Nature\'). The agonized face in the painting has become one of the most iconic images in art, seen as symbolizing the anxiety of the human condition. Munch\'s work, including The Scream, had a formative influence on the Expressionist movement.</string>
    <string name="mona_lisa_desc">The Mona Lisa[a] is a half-length portrait painting by the Italian artist Leonardo da Vinci. Considered an archetypal masterpiece of the Italian Renaissance,[4][5] it has been described as \"the best known, the most visited, the most written about, the most sung about, [and] the most parodied work of art in the world.\"[6] The painting\'s novel qualities include the subject\'s enigmatic expression,[7] monumentality of the composition, the subtle modelling of forms, and the atmospheric illusionism.</string>
    <string name="starry_night_desc">The Starry Night, often called simply Starry Night, is an oil-on-canvas painting by the Dutch Post-Impressionist painter Vincent van Gogh. Painted in June 1889, it depicts the view from the east-facing window of his asylum room at Saint-Rémy-de-Provence, just before sunrise, with the addition of an imaginary village.[1][2] It has been in the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art in New York City since 1941,[3] acquired through the Lillie P. Bliss Bequest. Described as a \"touchstone of modern art\", The Starry Night has been regarded as one of the most recognizable paintings in the Western canon.</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>

    <!--   For Affirmations App Activity-->
    <string name="affirmation1">I am strong.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">I believe in myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Each day is a new opportunity to grow and be a better version of myself.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">Every challenge in my life is an opportunity to learn from.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">I have so much to be grateful for.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Good things are always coming into my life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">New opportunities await me at every turn.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">I have the courage to follow my heart.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">Things will unfold at precisely the right time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">I will be present in all the moments that this day brings.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_affirmations">AffirmationsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_topic_app">TopicAppActivity</string>

    <!--    For Topic App Activity-->
    <string name="architecture">Architecture</string>
    <string name="crafts">Crafts</string>
    <string name="business">Business</string>
    <string name="culinary">Culinary</string>
    <string name="design">Design</string>
    <string name="fashion">Fashion</string>
    <string name="film">Film</string>
    <string name="gaming">Gaming</string>
    <string name="drawing">Drawing</string>
    <string name="lifestyle">Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="painting">Painting</string>
    <string name="photography">Photography</string>
    <string name="tech">Tech</string>
    <string name="title_activity_woof">WoofActivity</string>

    <!--    Woof App Activity-->
    <string name="dog_name_1">Koda</string>
    <string name="dog_name_2">Lola</string>
    <string name="dog_name_3">Frankie</string>
    <string name="dog_name_4">Nox</string>
    <string name="dog_name_5">Faye</string>
    <string name="dog_name_6">Bella</string>
    <string name="dog_name_7">Moana</string>
    <string name="dog_name_8">Tzeitel</string>
    <string name="dog_name_9">Leroy</string>
    <string name="dog_description_1">Eating treats on the terrace</string>
    <string name="dog_description_2">Barking at Daddy</string>
    <string name="dog_description_3">Stealing socks</string>
    <string name="dog_description_4">Meeting new animals</string>
    <string name="dog_description_5">Digging in the garden</string>
    <string name="dog_description_6">Chasing sea foam</string>
    <string name="dog_description_7">Bothering her paw-rents</string>
    <string name="dog_description_8">Sunbathing</string>
    <string name="dog_description_9">Sleeping in dangerous places</string>
    <string name="about">About:</string>
    <string name="years_old">%d years old</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a dog.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_super_hero_app">SuperHeroAppActivity</string>

    <!--    Super Hero App-->
    <string name="super_hero_app_name">Superheroes</string>
    <string name="hero1">Nick the Night and Day</string>
    <string name="description1">The Jetpack Hero</string>
    <string name="hero2">Reality Protector</string>
    <string name="description2">Understands the absolute truth</string>
    <string name="hero3">Andre the Giant</string>
    <string name="description3">Mimics the light and night to blend in</string>
    <string name="hero4">Benjamin the Brave</string>
    <string name="description4">Harnesses the power of canary to develop bravely</string>
    <string name="hero5">Magnificent Maru</string>
    <string name="description5">Effortlessly glides in to save the day</string>
    <string name="hero6">Dynamic Yasmine</string>
    <string name="description6">Ability to shift to any form and energize</string>

    <!--    30 Days of Wellness App -->
    <string name="wellness_day_app_name">30 Days of Wellness</string>

    <string name="day1_title">Mindful Morning</string>
    <string name="day1_description">Start your day with 5 minutes of mindful breathing. Focus on your breath and nothing else.</string>
    <string name="day2_title">Hydration Boost</string>
    <string name="day2_description">Drink a large glass of water immediately after waking up to kickstart your metabolism.</string>
    <string name="day3_title">Stretch &amp; Move</string>
    <string name="day3_description">Engage in 10 minutes of gentle stretching. Focus on your major muscle groups.</string>
    <string name="day4_title">Healthy Breakfast</string>
    <string name="day4_description">Prepare a nutritious breakfast. Include protein, fiber, and healthy fats.</string>
    <string name="day5_title">Digital Detox</string>
    <string name="day5_description">Take a 1-hour break from all screens. Read a book, go for a walk, or meditate.</string>
    <string name="day6_title">Express Gratitude</string>
    <string name="day6_description">Write down three things you are grateful for today. Focus on the positive aspects of your life.</string>
    <string name="day7_title">Outdoor Time</string>
    <string name="day7_description">Spend at least 15 minutes outdoors today. Connect with nature and get some fresh air.</string>
    <string name="day8_title">Active Listening</string>
    <string name="day8_description">Practice active listening in one conversation today. Give your full attention to the speaker.</string>
    <string name="day9_title">Learn Something New</string>
    <string name="day9_description">Dedicate 30 minutes to learning something new, whether it\'s a language, skill, or topic of interest.</string>
    <string name="day10_title">Healthy Snack Prep</string>
    <string name="day10_description">Prepare healthy snacks for the week ahead to avoid unhealthy choices when hungry.</string>
    <string name="day11_title">Declutter a Space</string>
    <string name="day11_description">Choose one small area in your home and declutter it for 15 minutes. A tidy space can lead to a tidy mind.</string>
    <string name="day12_title">Mindful Eating</string>
    <string name="day12_description">Eat one meal mindfully today. Savor each bite, paying attention to flavors and textures.</string>
    <string name="day13_title">Connect with a Loved One</string>
    <string name="day13_description">Reach out to a friend or family member you haven\'t spoken to in a while. A quick call or text can make a difference.</string>
    <string name="day14_title">Review Your Goals</string>
    <string name="day14_description">Take 10 minutes to review your personal goals. Are you on track? What adjustments can you make?</string>
    <string name="day15_title">Light Cardio</string>
    <string name="day15_description">Engage in 20 minutes of light cardio, such as brisk walking, cycling, or dancing.</string>
    <string name="day16_title">Journal Your Thoughts</string>
    <string name="day16_description">Spend 15 minutes journaling. Write down your thoughts, feelings, or anything on your mind.</string>
    <string name="day17_title">Plan Your Week</string>
    <string name="day17_description">Dedicate time to plan your week ahead. Organize your tasks, appointments, and self-care activities.</string>
    <string name="day18_title">Try a New Recipe</string>
    <string name="day18_description">Cook a new, healthy recipe today. Expand your culinary horizons and enjoy nutritious food.</string>
    <string name="day19_title">Digital Sunset</string>
    <string name="day19_description">Put away all screens 1 hour before bedtime. Allow your mind to wind down naturally.</string>
    <string name="day20_title">Practice Forgiveness</string>
    <string name="day20_description">Practice forgiving someone, or yourself, for something small. Let go of resentment.</string>
    <string name="day21_title">Nature Walk</string>
    <string name="day21_description">Go for a walk in a park or natural setting. Observe your surroundings and breathe deeply.</string>
    <string name="day22_title">Positive Affirmations</string>
    <string name="day22_description">Repeat three positive affirmations to yourself throughout the day. "I am capable," "I am strong," etc.</string>
    <string name="day23_title">Prioritize Sleep</string>
    <string name="day23_description">Aim for 7-9 hours of quality sleep tonight. Create a relaxing bedtime routine.</string>
    <string name="day24_title">Limit Processed Foods</string>
    <string name="day24_description">Make a conscious effort to reduce or eliminate processed foods from your diet today.</string>
    <string name="day25_title">Meditation Session</string>
    <string name="day25_description">Try a guided meditation for 10-15 minutes. Many apps and videos are available.</string>
    <string name="day26_title">Random Act of Kindness</string>
    <string name="day26_description">Perform a small, random act of kindness for someone else today. Pay it forward.</string>
    <string name="day27_title">Set Boundaries</string>
    <string name="day27_description">Identify one area where you need to set a boundary (e.g., work, social media) and commit to it.</string>
    <string name="day28_title">Review Progress</string>
    <string name="day28_description">Look back at your wellness journey so far. Acknowledge your progress and learn from challenges.</string>
    <string name="day29_title">Future Self Letter</string>
    <string name="day29_description">Write a letter to your future self, outlining your hopes, dreams, and wellness goals.</string>
    <string name="day30_title">Celebrate &amp; Reflect</string>
    <string name="day30_description">Celebrate completing 30 days of wellness! Reflect on what you\'ve learned and plan next steps.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_wellness_day">WellnessDayActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_dessert_clicker">DessertClickerActivity</string>

    <string name="dessert_sold">Desserts sold</string>
    <string name="total_revenue">Total Revenue</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_text">I\'ve clicked %1$d Desserts for a total of $%2$d #AndroidDessertClicker</string>
    <string name="sharing_not_available">Sharing Not Available</string>
    <string name="title_activity_unscramble">UnscrambleActivity</string>

    <string name="unscramble_app_name">Unscramble</string>
    <string name="instructions">Unscramble the word using all the letters.</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="score">Score: %d</string>
    <string name="word_count">%d/10</string>
    <string name="enter_your_word">Enter your word</string>
    <string name="congratulations">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="you_scored">"You scored: %d"</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="wrong_guess">Wrong Guess!</string>

</resources>